<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--
Greenbone Security Assistant
$Id$
Description: German translations of strings.

Authors:
Jan-Oliver Wagner <Jan-Oliver.Wagner@greenbone.net>

Copyright:
Copyright (C) 2013 Greenbone Networks GmbH

This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or modify
it under the terms of the GNU General Public License version 2,
or, at your option, any later version as published by the Free
Software Foundation

This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful,
but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of
MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE.  See the
GNU General Public License for more details.

You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License
along with this program; if not, write to the Free Software
Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 02110-1301 USA.
-->

<i18n>
  <msg>
    <id>Apply overrides</id>
    <str>Übersteuerung anwenden</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Logged in as</id>
    <str>Angemeldet als</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Logout</id>
    <str>Abmelden</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>New Task</id>
    <str>Neue Aufgabe</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Notes</id>
    <str>Notizen</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Overrides</id>
    <str>Übersteuerungen</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Report: Summary</id>
    <str>Bericht: Übersicht</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Targets</id>
    <str>Ziele</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Tasks</id>
    <str>Aufgaben</str>
  </msg>

  <!-- wizard.xsl -->

  <msg>
    <id>Task Wizard</id>
    <str>Aufgaben-Wizard</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Welcome dear new user!</id>
    <str>Willkommen neue Anwender!</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>
      To explore this powerful application and to
      have a quick start for doing things the first time,
      I am here to assist you with some hints and short-cuts.
    </id>
    <str>
      Um die umfangreichen Möglichkeiten dieser Anwendung kennenzulernen
      und um schnell erste Ergebnisse zu erzielen, helfe ich
      mit Hinweisen und Abkürzungen.
    </str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>I will appear automatically in areas where you have
          created no or only a few objects. And disappear when you
          have more than
    </id>
    <str>Ich erscheine automatisch dort wo noch keine oder nur wenige
            Objekte vorliegen. Und verschwinde wieder wenn mehr als</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>objects. You can call me with this icon</id>
    <str>Objekte vorliegen. Ich kann aber über dieses Icon</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>any time later on.</id>
    <str>jederzeit wieder aktiviert werden.</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>For more detailed information
          on functionality, please try the integrated help system. It is
          always available as a context sensitive link as icon
    </id>
    <str>Für detaillierte Information zu den Funktionen steht das
            integrierte Hilfe-System zur Verfügung. Diese steht jederzeit
            kontext-bezogen über das Hilfe-Icon bereit:
            </str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Quick start: Immediately scan an IP address</id>
    <str>Schnellstart: Unmittelbar eine IP-Adresse scannen</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>IP address or hostname:</id>
    <str>IP-Adresse oder Hostname:</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>For this short-cut I will do the following for you:</id>
    <str>Für diese Abkürzung werde ich folgendes durchführen:</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Create a new Target with default Port List</id>
    <str>Erstellen eines neuen Ziels mit voreingestellter Port-Liste</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Create a new Task using this target with default Scan Configuration</id>
    <str>Erstellen einer neuen Aufgabe mit diesem Ziel und voreingestellter Scan-Konfiguration</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Start this scan task right away</id>
    <str>Direktes Starten dieser Scan-Aufgabe</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>Switch the view to reload every 30 seconds so you can lean back and watch the scan progress</id>
    <str>Wechseln der Ansicht auf Seitenaktualisierung alle 30 Sekunden so dass man sich zurücklehnen und dem Scan-Fortschritt zuschauen kann</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>In fact, you must not lean back.
          As soon as the scan progress is beyond 1%,
          you can already jump into the scan report via the link in the name column</id>
    <str>Im Grunde muss man sich aber nicht zurücklehnen. Sobald der Scan-Fortschritt
            über 1% liegt kann man bereits in die Details des Scan-Berichts</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>and review the results collected so far.</id>
    <str>springen</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>By clicking the New Task icon</id>
    <str>Durch Anklicken des &quot;Neue Aufgabe&quot;-Icons</str>
  </msg>
  <msg>
    <id>you can also create a new Task yourself. However, you will also need a Target first, which you can create by going to the Targets page found in the Configuration menu and clicking the New Target icon</id>
    <str>kann man Aufgaben auch selbst erstellen. Hierfür wird jedoch auch ein Ziel benötigt, welches erstellt werden kann, indem man auf der Ziele-Seite aus den Konfigurations-Menü auf das Icon &quot;Neues Ziel&quot; klickt</str>
  </msg>

</i18n>
